https://heimerdingercutlery.com/privacy-policy/

$0.00
Search for:
Search for:
Global knives
Victorinox (Forschner)
Global knives
Victorinox (Forschner)
Magnifying mirrors
Floxite Replacement bulbs()
Magnifying mirrors
Floxite Replacement bulbs()
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy for The Heimerdinger Cutlery Company Incorporated and its Subsidiaries and Affiliates (“Heimerdinger Cutlery”)
Heimerdinger Cutlery Company Incorporated is committed to protecting your privacy. The information you provide is primarily used to enhance your experience at Heimerdinger Cutlery Company Incorporated properties. We may use it to update you on products and services provided by us and our merchants, remind you of important occasions, and/or personalize your shopping experience. The information may also be used internally for research and business development purposes, statistical analysis and to improve this web site, Heimerdinger Cutlery Company Incorporated’s marketing and promotional efforts and business operations. This statement outlines our privacy policies and explains what information we collect from our users and why (our “Policy”). When you use our web site or register with us (including by completing an entry form), you agree to abide by the terms of this Policy and any relevant terms of use. We may make changes to this Policy from time to time. Any changes to this Policy will be available at the customer service facilities at our centers and/or on this web page. If you have any questions about this Policy, our privacy protection practices, or your dealings with us, please feel free to contact us by sending an e-mail to contact@heimerdingercutlery.com or contact the customer services facility at the applicable center.
The core of our Policy is this: Heimerdinger Cutlery Company Incorporated will not knowingly release, sell, rent or trade your personal information to any third party without your permission, except to our merchants (which includes our business partners), as discussed herein or if we believe in good faith that the law requires it, or to protect our own rights and properties. Heimerdinger Cutlery Company Incorporated considers personal information to include, without limitation, name, e-mail address, home or mailing address, phone number, birth date, anniversary date, or other similar information you may provide to us (your “Personal Information”).
Please note that if you provide any Personal Information to any third party web site linked to or from this site, the privacy of that Personal Information will not be covered by this policy, and may be subject to the privacy policy of the operator of that third party web site, if any.
What Information We Collect and How We Use It:
Heimerdinger Cutlery Company Incorporated collects Personal Information on a voluntary basis. In order to take advantage of some of our features, programs or events you may need to register and/or provide Personal Information before you can participate. We and/or our merchants will use this Personal Information to send you e-mails, newsletters or other communications from us and/or our merchants and to inform you about special offers, programs or events that might interest you.
We may also sometimes provide Personal Information to our merchants so that they are able to contact you and make you aware of sales, specials, promotions or other opportunities. You should note that we don’t control these operators or their privacy policies, and that if you do not wish to receive communications from them, you should contact them directly.
You always have the option to change your mind about receiving communications from us, or to change or update any of your Personal Information, by e-mailing us at contact@heimerdingercutlery.comor contacting the customer services facility at the applicable center, and submitting the appropriate changes.
Heimerdinger Cutlery Company Incorporated maintains internal controls in order to limit any unauthorized access to Personal Information you provide to us. These can include firewalls and other security features.
Your Responsibility:
Although we will protect your privacy on our site as described in this Policy, you should keep in mind that if you voluntarily disclose Personal Information online, that information may be accessible to others. This is also true if anyone else has access to your personal computer, such as an employer or family member. However, if you link to a third party site from our site, any information you reveal on that site is not subject to this Policy. You should consult the privacy policies of each site you visit. In addition, Heimerdinger Cutlery Company Incorporated is not responsible for the content of any sites that may be linked to Heimerdinger Cutlery Company Incorporated’s site.
Use of Cookies:
Heimerdinger Cutlery Company Incorporated and/or its merchants, like many companies, may use cookies to enhance your experience while using their web sites. Cookies make using our site easier by storing and tracking your preferences and passwords. Cookies are stored on your computer, and are not accessible to Heimerdinger Cutlery Company Incorporated or any other site you may visit.
Your browser is probably set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can change your browser settings to refuse them. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our site will not function properly when you view them, and you may have to enter Personal Information every time you use that site in order to participate in certain services or promotions.
Search for:
CONTACT USCustomer Service 502-897-9552
NEWSLETTERLeave this field empty if you're human:
FOLLOW US!
© 2020 Heimerdinger Cutlery All Rights Reserved.
